Now I know who your niece...
takes after.
I wonder if the Dechas can handle her.
May you be loved and cherished.
Still no letter from Thep?
One arrived this morning.
Why would she want it?
She can't even read or write.
I saw the Lady tear it up.
Knowing Thep thinks of us makes me happy.
What's wrong?
How disgraceful!
How can I be sure...
the baby is my grandchild?
Indeed, my Lady.
My aunt went to Chanthaburi
and sent some fruit.
Is this...
Bu-nga, how dare you steal
Lady Mok's bracelet?
I...
Did you find it?
Right here.
- But, I...
- It's always you!
First, you tried to kill the Lady.
Now you steal from Lady Mok.
You’re nothing but a born thief.
I really didn't do it.
You dare suspect me?
Because you think
I’m a wicked woman.
You do believe that...
this baby isn't your grandchild.
You’re just trying to get rid of me.
Lock her up.
Don't let her see the light of day.
- She's Thep's wife!
- Shut it, Khem!
Otherwise,
you’ll be punished as well.
Get her out of my sight.
Go!
She's a human being.
Shall we send her away?
I'm not going back.
I'll wait here for Thep here.
I can remember my past lives, right?
If you really can,
you must have seen it all.
I feel like someone else is in the house.
Someone... not human.
Put these on the front door,
the back door, and the bedroom.
Understood.
What's...
that, Dad?
Ploy!
You can never escape me.
You will pay for what you've done.
If death were the end,
who would pay me back?
Stay out of this!
I heard Thep is seeing her.
No wonder he won't come home.
Bu-nga! I said wake up!
- Auntie?
- Help!
Help me.
Bu-nga! She...
What's wrong with her?
She'was heartbroken
that you hadn't returned.
I'm still waiting for Thep.
Hey!
Bu-nga!!
Bu-nga!! No!
Help me!
Thep?
Did you have a nightmare?
I need to go home.
You need to recover first.
I'm worried about my wife and child.
Father.
Where is my baby?
The baby was born prematurely.
She’s a bit small.
But look.
She's a fighter.
Father.
Please take me to Thep.
I need to hear it from him...
that he no longer loves us.
Why would you say that?
Did you hear something?
Did the bleeding start...
because you heard something
upsetting?
I heard people saying...
that Thep...
is seeing another woman.
That's why he's not coming home.
I’ll go find him myself.
The moment I brought you here,
I decided...
I was going to find him.
Once he knows the baby's been born,
he'll come back.
If you suddenly disappear,
won't they be suspicious?
You have no relatives to visit.
I said I was visiting
a friend in Kantang.
Just be careful.
They have eyes everywhere.
If they find out,
you'll be in trouble.
Master Thep!
My Lord!
Where are you going?
I was going to find you in the capital.
Why?
What’s happened at home?
Bu-nga
- Bu-nga--
- Be careful, Thep.
What's wrong with her?
Khem!
Tell me! What happened?
Thep...
insisted on returning
His cast was just removed.
Ploy's been nursing him,
so she was worried.
Now that she had to come,
I'd tag along to visit you.
And Ploy can look after
her special patient.
Oh...
My dear.
You're so beautiful,
and so kind-hearted.
Do you remember?
We once...
met
at the play
Sao Khruea Fa
when the Pridalai Theatre first opened.
You were so small then.
Right?
I remember it vaguely, Auntie.
Auntie?
Just call me Mother.
Oh,
Thep.
I'll have Uncle Theng get the car ready.
Mother.
I know you never cared for Bu-nga.
But your grandchild is hospitalized.
Do you even care?
She’s fine now, right?
Must I watch over her?
It was life or death.
Why no telegram?
If I hadn't returned,
I’d never have known.
Thep,
can I visit Bu-nga, too?
Mok,
tell me exactly...
what happened?
At the hospital,
I'll tell you.
I'm taking my wife and child home.
You sure?
Aren't you with another woman?
Did Khem tell you?
You know how he is.
He’s loyal to a fault.
The whole station saw you.
Before long,
The rumor spread all over.
Just family friends visiting.
- Is she being discharged?
- She's coming with me.
She only goes...
if the Lady...
comes for her.
Please double-check this.
Alright.
Now that I'm settled,
I'm taking Bu-nga and my daughter
with me to the capital.
You can't.
I've made an arrangement with Ploy.
I have a family of my own, Mother.
That doesn't matter.
Men often take a second wife.
Ploy and I don't love each other.
You clearly care for her.
That's not love.
What do you know of life?
Status matters more than love.
A wife who brings
you no honor...
will only bring regret.
No more arguing.
We have spoken. It’s settled.
Obey, or never mention Bu-nga again.
If that’s how it is,
then I’ll take them elsewhere.
Thep
Thep!
Wait, Duangkhae.
Calm down...
My...
No one listens to me here.
Thep
Thep!
Don't leave.
I’m done obeying you.
You lied to me about everything.
You were never honest with me.
I shouldn't have trusted her.
She loves you dearly.
She can't bear to lose you.
Please don't tell her...
that I told you everything.
Otherwise, I'll be kicked out, too.
You believe everything Bu-nga says?
Did she tell you
why I made her sleep downstairs?
Why I locked her up?
She stole Mok's bracelet,
and kept talking back to me.
Worse, she fed me eggs!
Did you hear me? She tried kill me!
Even so, I still let her stay.
I’ve been far too merciful.
You're biased.
You blame her for everything.
And aren't you biased against me?
Love has blinded you
so you think I'm framing her.
She never framed you.
Let's just say...
we'll part ways, as I've decided.
Hey!
- Enough, both of you!
- Thep!
- Wait!
- Let go of me!
Ah!
Ouch!
Mother!
- Duangkhae!
- Mother!
Sister!
Careful.
Alright.
You should go to bed.
I'll stay with Duangkhae.
But I should care for you tonight.
How can I leave her alone?
Duangkhae,
how are you feeling?
Well...
My wound still hurts.
I’m still a bit dizzy.
It's good we have a nurse here.
We won't need the hospital this late.
I think you should rest.
Don't overthink things for now.
If you'll go to the bathroom,
just call for him.
Okay.
I stop overthinking now.
From now on, everyone can do as they wish.
I’m getting old.
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
Can’t sleep either?
I didn't think coming here...
would cause so much trouble.
It's not your fault.
Mother never liked my wife anyway.
If it wasn't you,
she'd find someone else.
Is there anything I can do?
Should I take Auntie back sooner?
I have a favor to ask.
Let's get engaged.
Look.
Are you hungry?
Coming here is enough, right?
Yes.
It's been two weeks. Time flies.
I know.
But things were so chaotic.
I couldn't take you out anywhere.
Well...
Visit us after the ceremony.
Just...
finish up here so you can come soon.
Listen.
After everything,
I'll take you to a theatre every night.
Okay.
Please take care.
You too.
And don't forget to...
use the money I gave...
for powder and rouge.
Don't let me down.
Listen.
You know?
Songkhla girls are pretty
but you, Duangkhae...
are said to be
the most beautiful of them all.
You're exaggerating.
Alright.
Go check your bags.
Take good care of everyone.
I will.
Thank you for understanding.
Trust me...
A man can have many wives.
But a main wife must support your status,
and be worthy of honor.
Yes, Mother.
Careful.
I'll be going now.
Okay.
Goodbye, Auntie.
Safe travels.
I'm leaving now, Mother.
Have a safe trip, son.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Phon!
She went to the market.
What do you need?
Go fetch Bu-nga for me.
So everything went smoothly...
because you faked the engagement?
Yes.
Thep already made a deal with Ploy.
Let's get engaged.
But not married.
I just need time to take my family...
and settle down in the capital.
It'll take about three months.
Then you can call it off.
After that,
all the engagement gifts...
will be yours.
I own a house in Chonburi.
It's not big,
but please take it as a thank-you.
I don't want any of those things.
What do you want?
Just tell me.
If I can,
I'll give you everything.
What I want,
you cannot give me.
Let's just say I'll help.
Tell Auntie that we're getting engaged.
I'm happy to help.
Thank you so much.
I will never forget your kindness.
Think carefully, Bu-nga.
No one accepts a broken engagement.
They fear losing their honor.
Then...
why would Ploy
agree to help?
My,
you're so naive.
If she refuses to call it off,
no one can stop her.
You know that...
the Lady is on their side.
Are they...
tricking you?
Look.
The night the Lady got hurt,
I saw them together on the lawn.
You must have been mistaken.
Thep wouldn't do that.
He's a gentleman,
if a girl throws herself at him,
he’ll give in eventually.
If I hadn't trusted all of you,
I wouldn't be suffering like this.
What did you just say?
I said,
Chan is a good girl.
Yes, she's very sweet.
Never stubborn or pouty.
If no one plays with her,
she’s happy playing by herself.
But she has a condition,
just like I told you.
You could say she's easy...
or a handful at the same time.
My bad.
How long have you known
this place is off?
Is that why you sold it?
If I knew it was haunted,
would I stay and end up hospitalized?
I agree.
I'm sorry.
I was clueless...
until I found this watch...
and tried to sell it.
The fortune teller said...
everything...
stems from a curse.
But I have no idea
who cursed my family.
What’s that got to do with you?
Peekaboo!
Mother!
Is it because I'm still here?
If I leave, will this end?
For you, maybe.
But for me,
it's a curse.
What should we do?
I need to find out...
who cursed my family.
Did Mom bring Uncle Jomthap home?
Yes, dear.
Oh, I forgot to mention...
A friend is staying with me.
His name is Jomthap
Chanchao
really likes him.
I'm not superstitious.
Just a bit spiritual.
Will you let me in?
It would be cruel to keep you outside.
Say that you permit me to enter.
You have permission to enter.
I give you permission, too.
Uncle!
What is it?
Chanchao,
how are you doing?
Busaban wants to earn extra cash.
So I hired her for chores and babysitting.
You'll have more time to work...
and...
focus on whatever you want.
She seems a bit odd to me.
A bit, given her troubled past.
But she's harmless.
Actually, she’s just pitiful.
It's her,
the student I told you about.
The one from a poor family.
She doesn't even have a computer.
I thought it was a guy.
No,
it's her.
Is this room empty?
I'll stay here.
Do you know her too?
No.
Thep isn't that kind of man.
Help!
Is anyone there? Help!
Help! Open up! Help!
Master?
Keep this for emergencies.
I gave some to Bu-nga, too.
I’m afraid Mother might take it.
You’re the only one I can trust.
On this trip to the capital,
I have a bad feeling.
Protect my wife and child.
Can I...
ask a question?
Please be honest.
You and...
Ploy.
She’s like a sister to me.
I don't feel that way about her.
Khem,
I put the address of my home there
and the ministry's...
in the money pouch.
If anything comes up,
telegram me immediately.
I'll also write to my friend, Somkid.
Mother won't suspect a thing.
Ah!
Have you found Ploy?
No sign of her.
Did a student named Busaban
attend the exam this morning?
Our faculty...
has no student by that name.
Is she in our major?
She always sits here.
I've even used this computer.
But that one's been broken
since last term.
Are you sure it's this room?
Ah!
They're tying the knot any day now.
Fool, you’ve been tricked again.
Your marriage is a wreck,
so you hate seeing others happy.
How dare you!
Bu-nga!
Once Thep marries Ploy,
she'll see the truth
and see right from wrong.
Is something wrong?
His Highness is hosting our wedding.
The reason she...
moved you up here...
was to build a house for her favorite.
What's so special about her?
She's not as pretty as you.
Maybe she used black magic
on them both.
We can't just sit back and take this.
You really have to marry another woman...
even though you have a wife and child?
I meant no disrespect!
Please don't hurt me!
You died and forgot everything.
But I'm the only one who remembers.
Look at me.